<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MuseMad</string>
    <string name="Login">LOGIN</string>
    <string name="Register">REGISTER</string>
    <string name="SubtituloLogin">Log in or enter as a guest to discover the museums of Madrid:</string>
    <string name="SubtituloRegister">Register or enter as a guest to discover the museums of Madrid:</string>
    <string name="Email">E-mail</string>
    <string name="Passw">Password</string>
    <string name="cPassw">Confirm Password</string>
    <string name="cLogin">Log in</string>
    <string name="Guest">Guest</string>
    <string name="eRegist">Register here</string>
    <string name="cRegist">Register</string>

    <string name="descPrado">The Prado is famous for its impressive collection of Spanish paintings. You can admire works by artists such as Diego Velázquez, Francisco de Goya, El Greco, and Bartolomé Esteban Murillo.</string>
    <string name="descReinaSofia">The Reina Sofía National Museum of Art is one of Madrid\'s leading contemporary art museums. It houses masterpieces such as the famous painting "Guernica" by Pablo Picasso, along with a wide collection of modern and contemporary art.</string>
    <string name="descThyssen">The Thyssen-Bornemisza Museum exhibits a vast collection of art spanning from the Renaissance to the 20th century. Here you can enjoy works by artists such as Rembrandt, Van Gogh, Monet, and Picasso, among others.</string>
    <string name="descSorolla">The Sorolla Museum is dedicated to the Spanish painter Joaquín Sorolla. Here you can appreciate a wide selection of his works, including his famous landscapes, portraits, and beach scenes.</string>
    <string name="descArqueologico">El Museo Arqueológico Nacional ofrece una fascinante visión de la historia de España y otras civilizaciones a través de sus exhibiciones de artefactos arqueológicos, incluyendo piezas prehistóricas, romanas, griegas y visigodas.</string>
    <string name="descHistoriaMadrid">The Museum of the History of Madrid invites you to explore the city\'s history from ancient times to the present day through artifacts, documents, and artworks showcasing the evolution of the Spanish capital.</string>
    <string name="descAmerica">The Museum of the Americas exhibits an extensive collection of art and artifacts from pre-Columbian cultures of the Americas, as well as from the colonial and contemporary periods. It\'s a fascinating window into the history and cultural diversity of the continent.</string>
    <string name="descAntropologia">The National Museum of Anthropology offers a global perspective on world cultures, with a wide collection of ethnographic and anthropological artifacts showcasing the diversity of traditions and customs of different peoples and civilizations.</string>
    <string name="descCerralbo">The Cerralbo Museum is a 19th-century mansion housing the private collection of art and antiques belonging to the Marquis of Cerralbo. Here you can admire furniture, paintings, sculptures, and decorative objects offering insight into the art and daily life of the period.</string>
    <string name="descNaval">The Naval Museum of Madrid is a space dedicated to the history of the Spanish navy, with a wide collection of ship models, cartography, uniforms, and artifacts related to navigation and naval warfare.</string>
    <string name="descCienciasNaturales">The Museum of Natural Sciences of Madrid invites you to explore the planet\'s biodiversity through its exhibitions on geology, paleontology, zoology, and botany. Here you can discover fossils, minerals, taxidermy animals, and much more.</string>
    <string name="descTraje">The Costume Museum is dedicated to the history and evolution of clothing and fashion in Spain. With a collection ranging from traditional costumes to contemporary designs, it offers a fascinating look at the world of attire over time.</string>
    <string name="descArtesDecorativas">The National Museum of Decorative Arts exhibits a selection of furniture, ceramics, textiles, glass, and other decorative objects showcasing the evolution of art and design in Spain and other countries over the centuries.</string>
    <string name="descFerrocarril">The Railway Museum takes you on a journey through the history of railway transportation in Spain, with an impressive collection of locomotives, carriages, models, and objects related to the railroad.</string>
    <string name="descSanIsidro">The San Isidro Museum is located in the Casa de San Isidro, a historic building that was the residence of Madrid\'s patron saint. Here you can learn about the city\'s history and culture through exhibitions on archaeology, medieval art, and everyday life during San Isidros time.</string>
    <string name="descABC">The ABC Museum is a space dedicated to drawing and illustration, with a wide collection of works by Spanish and international artists. Here you can enjoy temporary exhibitions and activities related to the art of drawing and graphic storytelling.</string>
    <string name="descLazaroGaldiano">The Lázaro Galdiano Museum houses the private art collection of entrepreneur José Lázaro Galdiano, including paintings, sculptures, furniture, decorative objects, and decorative arts from different periods and styles.</string>
    <string name="descRomanticismo">The National Museum of Romanticism invites you to travel to the 19th century and explore the life and art of the romantic period in Spain. With a collection including paintings, furniture, dresses, and everyday objects, it offers a fascinating look at this historical period.</string>
    <string name="descArteRomano">The National Museum of Roman Art in Mérida is one of Spain\'s main archaeological museums. Here you can admire an impressive collection of Roman artifacts, including sculptures, mosaics, inscriptions, and everyday objects.</string>
    <string name="descRealAcademia">The Museum of the Royal Academy of Fine Arts of San Fernando exhibits a selection of works from the Academy\'s collection, including paintings, sculptures, and drawings by Spanish and international artists.</string>
    <string name="descCiudad">The Museum of the City is located in the former Casa de la Villa de Madrid, a historic building that once housed the city council. Here you can learn about the history and evolution of the city through exhibitions on urban planning, architecture, and daily life.</string>
    <string name="descAire">The Air Museum is dedicated to the history of aviation in Spain, with a wide collection of airplanes, helicopters, engines, and other objects related to military and civil aviation.</string>
    <string name="descGeominero">The Geological Museum invites you to explore the fascinating world of geology, with a collection of minerals, rocks, fossils, and other objects related to Earth sciences.</string>
    <string name="descHistoriaArte">The Museum of Art History of Madrid offers a comprehensive view of Western art history, from antiquity to the present day, through its exhibitions of paintings, sculptures, drawings, and other artistic objects.</string>
    <string name="descOrigenes">The Museum of Origins, also known as the Museum of San Isidro, is dedicated to the history of Madrid from its prehistoric origins to the present day. With a collection including archaeological artifacts, models, and reconstructions, it offers a fascinating insight into the city\'s evolution over time.</string>
    <string name="descReproducciones">The National Museum of Artistic Reproductions is a space dedicated to the reproduction of masterpieces from art history. Here you can admire reproductions of famous paintings, sculptures, and other artistic objects from different periods and styles.</string>
    <string name="descTeatro">The National Theater Museum offers a comprehensive view of the history of theater in Spain, with a collection including costumes, models, programs, posters, and other objects related to the world of theater.</string>
    <string name="descBibliotecaNacional">The Museum of the National Library of Spain invites you to explore the history of the book and writing through its exhibitions of manuscripts, incunabula, rare books, and other objects related to bibliophilia and the history of the book.</string>
    <string name="descFabricaTapices">The Museum of the Royal Tapestry Factory offers a fascinating insight into the history of tapestry in Spain, with a collection of tapestries, looms, tools, and other objects related to this ancient craft tradition.</string>
    <string name="descFundacionLazaroGaldiano">The Museum of the Lázaro Galdiano Foundation houses the private art and antique collection of entrepreneur José Lázaro Galdiano, including paintings, sculptures, furniture, decorative objects, and decorative arts from different periods and styles.</string>
    <string name="descEsculturaAireLibre">The Museum of Outdoor Sculpture on Castellana Avenue is a public space dedicated to contemporary sculpture, with a collection of works by Spanish and international artists exhibited along Madrid\'s Castellana Avenue.</string>
    <string name="descAcademiaBellasArtes">The Museum of the Academy of Fine Arts of San Fernando exhibits a selection of works from the Academy\'s collection, including paintings, sculptures, and drawings by Spanish and international artists.</string>
    <string name="descBomberos">The Firefighters Museum is dedicated to the history and evolution of firefighting services in Spain, with a collection of vehicles, uniforms, tools, and other objects related to fire fighting.</string>
    <string name="descFarmaciaHispana">The Museum of Hispanic Pharmacy offers a comprehensive view of the history of pharmacy in Spain, with a collection of apothecaries, utensils, books, and other objects related to pharmaceutical practice over the centuries.</string>
    <string name="descRatoncitoPerez">The Tooth Fairy Museum is dedicated to the famous character from Spanish folklore. Here you can learn about the history and legends related to the Tooth Fairy, as well as see a collection of objects related to him.</string>
    <string name="descCanalesIsabelII">The Isabel II Canal Museum invites you to explore the history and engineering of water supply systems in Madrid, with a collection of models, tools, photographs, and other objects related to water channels and conduits.</string>
    <string name="descHistoriaFarmacia">The Museum of Pharmacy History takes you on a journey through the history of medicine and pharmacy in Spain, with a collection of utensils, apothecaries, books, and other objects related to pharmaceutical practice over the centuries.</string>
    <string name="descEvolucionHumana">The Museum of Human Evolution invites you to explore the history of humanity and biological evolution through its exhibitions on paleontology, anthropology, and archaeology. Here you can discover fossils, tools, and other traces of our ancestors.</string>
    <string name="descFundacionTelefonica">The Museum of the Telefonica Foundation offers a glimpse into the history of communications in Spain, with a collection of telephones, transmission equipment, photographs, and other objects related to telephony and information technology.</string>
    <string name="descVino">The Wine Museum takes you on a journey through the history and culture of wine in Spain, with a collection of tools, utensils, bottles, labels, and other objects related to viticulture and oenology.</string>
    <string name="descJamon">The Ham Museum is dedicated to the history and culture of ham in Spain, with a collection of tools, utensils, posters, labels, and other objects related to the production, marketing, and consumption of this delicious product.</string>
    <string name="descDeporte">The Sports Museum invites you to explore the history and culture of sports in Spain, with a collection of trophies, medals, equipment, photographs, and other objects related to different sports disciplines.</string>
    <string name="descMODO">The Museum of the Object of the Object (MODO) is a space dedicated to design, advertising, and visual communication. Here you can admire a wide collection of everyday objects that showcase the evolution of design and material culture over time.</string>
    <string name="descBNE">The Museum of the BNE (National Library of Spain) offers a comprehensive view of the history of the book and writing through its exhibitions of manuscripts, incunabula, rare books, and other objects related to bibliophilia and the history of the book.</string>
    <string name="descAutomovil">The Automobile Museum takes you on a journey through the history and evolution of the automobile in Spain, with a collection of vintage, classic, and period cars, as well as other objects related to the automotive industry.</string>
    <string name="descCera">The Wax Museum of Madrid invites you to meet your favorite characters, with a collection of wax figures of celebrities, historical figures, athletes, politicians, and film and television stars.</string>
    <string name="descArteContemporaneo">The Museum of Contemporary Art of the Ministry of Culture offers a glimpse into the contemporary art scene in Spain, with a collection of works by Spanish and international artists representing different trends and artistic movements.</string>


</resources>